So let's just get started and talk about some phrases we can use to disagree how we can actually express
因此，让我们开始讨论一些我们可以用来反对我们如何实际表达的短语
our disagreement and there are a couple of simple ways we can do it.
我们的分歧，我们可以通过几种简单的方法来做到这一点。
There are many many possibilities many possible ways but we're going to go through a couple of common
有很多可能性很多可能的方法，但我们将通过几个常见的
phrases common phrases.
短语 常用短语。
One is that we don't we don't see eye to eye.
一个是我们不同意，我们没有意见一致。
If you think about it the phrase eye to eye does make sense.
如果您考虑一下，“眼睛对眼睛”这个词确实是有道理的。
My eyes lined up with your eye.
我的眼睛和你的眼睛对齐。
We kind of have the same view.
我们有相同的看法。
So you can kind of understand the idea.
所以你可以理解这个想法。
It means if we say we don't see eye to eye that we have a different opinion so let's say two parents
这意味着如果我们说我们意见不一致，那么我们有不同的意见，所以假设有两个父母
disagree about how to raise their children.
不同意如何抚养孩子。
I think our son should study after class many many extra curricular activities.
我认为我们的儿子应该在课后学习很多课外活动。
I think he should take a lot of extra classes.
我认为他应该参加很多额外的课程。
The other parent says I disagree.
另一位家长说我不同意。
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
We should give him more free time.
我们应该给他更多的空闲时间。
Let him play more.
让他多玩。
We just don't see eye to eye.
我们只是意见不一致。
And maybe she's saying that maybe the wife is saying that to her friends maybe the husband is saying
也许她在说也许妻子在对她的朋友说也许丈夫在说
it to his friends later.
以后给他的朋友。
We don't see eye to eye about this thing.
我们在这件事上意见不一致。
We disagree.
我们不同意。
Very common phrase if you do agree can you say we see eye to eye if you can.
如果您同意，这是非常常见的短语，如果可以的话，您能否说我们意见一致。
I think we see eye to eye on this.
我认为我们对此意见一致。
I think we are pretty much eye to eye on this issue.
我认为我们在这个问题上几乎是一致的。
OK my my opinion or view couldn't be more different my opinion or view couldn't be more different.
好吧，我的观点或观点再不同不过了，我的观点或观点再不同了。
But this is really useful if we want to express that our opinion is so far away from the other person
但是，如果我们想表达我们的意见与他人相距甚远，这真的很有用
that it's like the opposite end of the spectrum a spectrum is when you have one side all the way over
就像光谱的另一端一样，当您一直拥有一侧时
here and this is maybe plus and one side all the way over here and this is minus and then some space
在这里，这可能是加号，一直到这里的一侧，这是减号，然后是一些空间
in between and the space in between is kind of fuzzy.
中间和中间的空间有点模糊。
You know this is right in the middle.
你知道这是在中间。
This is closer to plus this is closer to minus but it's a kind of a mix.
这更接近于正，这更接近于负，但它是一种混合。
OK so if I say my opinion or view couldn't be more different that means I'm way over here and you're
好的，所以如果我说我的意见或观点完全不同，那就意味着我在这里，你在
way over here opposite ends of the spectrum of opinion.
远在意见范围的两端。
If you're here then it could be more different.
如果你在这里，那么它可能会更加不同。
In fact should we say that it could.
事实上我们应该说它可以。
It could be more different my opinion could be more different.
可能会更加不同，我的意见可能会更加不同。
No we don't usually use that expression.
不，我们通常不使用该表达式。
We generally will say I couldn't disagree more but we could also say I couldn't agree more.
我们通常会说我不能同意更多，但我们也可以说我不能同意更多。
So sometimes if we're completely on the same page completely on the same page that means we totally
所以有时如果我们完全在同一页面上 完全在同一页面上 这意味着我们完全
agree.
同意。
I couldn't agree more or it's the opposite.
我完全同意，或者恰恰相反。
My opinion couldn't be more different.
我的看法完全不同。
Now what if we want to make it softer because we don't always want to express that we have a very different
现在，如果我们想让它变得更柔和怎么办，因为我们并不总是想表达我们有一个非常不同的
view from from other people and we might want to show that we have some differences but it's not extreme
从其他人的角度来看，我们可能想表明我们有一些差异，但这并不极端
it's not very strong.
它不是很强大。
Well we could say this is very soft.
好吧，我们可以说这是非常柔软的。
I'm I'm not sure I see it that way.
我不确定我是否这么认为。
You could also say I don't think I don't think I see it that way.
你也可以说我不认为我不这么认为。
I just don't see it that way.
我只是不这么看。
If you want to make it very very gentle very gentle very soft very indirect you could say I'm not sure.
如果你想让它非常非常温和非常温和非常柔软非常间接，你可以说我不确定。
I'm just not sure I see it that way.
我只是不确定我是这样看的。
OK so for example where colleagues and one person says well you know what.
好的，例如，同事和一个人说得很好，你知道什么。
I think that we should never have to work overtime.
我认为我们永远不应该加班。
We're here to work 40 hours a week 40 hours a week no more.
我们是每周工作 40 小时，不再每周工作 40 小时。
And another person who wants to maybe add more contribute more so that maybe the company will be more
另一个想要增加更多贡献的人，也许公司会更多
successful.
成功的。
Maybe we'll say very politely I'm not sure I see it that way.
也许我们会很有礼貌地说我不确定我是否这么认为。
I think if we work overtime the whole company will be more productive and we're getting paid and we're
我认为如果我们加班，整个公司的工作效率会更高，我们会得到报酬，而且我们会
getting paid.
获取报酬。
Common expressions see eye to eye or don't see eye to eye.
常见的表达方式一致或不一致。
I couldn't agree more or my opinion couldn't be more different.
我完全同意，或者我的意见完全不同。
I'm not sure I see it that way.
我不确定我是这样看的。
OK.
好的。
Let's move on and actually look at a compromise.
让我们继续前进，看看一个折衷方案。
We'll talk about what that means and also some phrases that we can use to express compromise.
我们将讨论这意味着什么，以及我们可以用来表达妥协的一些短语。